<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Martin Labs</title>
    <link>https://martinlabs.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Martin Labs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 23:09:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://martinlabs.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back on 2023</title>
      <link>https://martinlabs.io/docs/131223/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 23:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinlabs.io/docs/131223/</guid>
      <description>What a year! I started off this year knowing very little about Openstack, Ansible and Terraform to presenting at the Computing Insight 2023 conference on the topic of Automated Deployment of Manufacturing Use-Cases through Openstack HPC. This demonstrated how we (The Manufacturing Technology Centre) managed to develop a platform that gave our engineers more autonomy via self-service infrastructure, allowing the Informatics and Modelling and Simulation teams to spend less time requesting their compute and more time doing their project work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://martinlabs.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martinlabs.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am Neil 🤓.
I am a Research Engineer at the Manufacturing Technology Centre and based within Merseyside in the UK. I sit within the Informatics department and specialise in cloud computing, high performance computing and distributed systems. I mostly use Openstack and Microsoft Azure in my day-to-day work but I am keen to get my teeth stuck into AWS at some point!
I enjoy using platforms and tools like Kubernetes, OpenTofu, Ansible to help businesses scale their infrastructure with good practice or make their overhead bureacracy chains shorter by implementing self service infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
